<location>
    <id>sevgard</id>
    <exploration>
        <id>farmfields</id>
        <name>Farmfields</name>
        <enabled>true</enabled>
        <image>true</image>
        <first>
            <![CDATA[
Farmfields is a large, fertile vale nestled outside Sevgard's stone walls. Sevgard operates under a form of feudalism and provides farmers with land, supplies, and protection in exchange for fresh produce and meat. This relationship has thrived for centuries and has allowed Sevgard to become a prosperous city.
            ]]>
        </first>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
Farmfields is a large, fertile vale nestled outside Sevgard's stone walls. Sevgard operates under a form of feudalism and provides farmers with land, supplies, and protection in exchange for fresh produce and meat. This relationship has thrived for centuries and has allowed Sevgard to become a prosperous city.

On its own, Farmfields is a quaint, cooperative community. The fields are divided into plots with sturdy fences built around them, and each plot contains a different crop, guarded by a stout scarecrow. For every few plots, there is a green pasture for cattle, horses, goats, and sheep to graze. Their manure is then used to fertilize the fields which gives the land a natural, earthy scent. One central irrigation system supplies the fields from the Hister River and its tributaries. The Hister flows strong throughout the year and keeps the crops refreshed during the warm season. What is more, an inn was established to accommodate travelers, and it is stationed beside the farmers' market where business is conducted.

From sunrise to sunset, the farmers can be found in their fields plowing, seeding, weeding, or harvesting. There is always work to be done. With their ever expanding fields, they require extra farmhands and will offer their hospitality for a hard day's work. Wheat is the predominant crop, and when the wind blows, the wheat sways like a tumultuous wave. As a result, the locals nicknamed the fields the Golden Sea. It is an especially breathtaking sight when the sun is setting, and the fields seem to glow in the dying light.

By nightfall, lanterns are lit on posts to prevent weary travelers from drifting astray. Despite Sevgard's age old vow to protect its farmers, the guards have become lax in their patrols. More bandits, goblins, and orcs have been roaming the countryside after dark.
            ]]>
        </description>
        <level>
            <minimum>1</minimum>
            <maximum>5</maximum>
        </level>
    </exploration>
    <exploration>
        <id>whispering_woods</id>
        <name>Whispering woods</name>
        <enabled>true</enabled>
        <image>true</image>
        <first>
            <![CDATA[
The Whispering Wood is an ancient forest lying on the edge of Farmfields. For generations, the ash and oaks have supplied Sevgard with thick, durable lumber and inspired many artists by their vibrant colors. When the harvest moon arrives, the woodcutters chop trees mercilessly, yet they regrow by the snow's thaw.
            ]]>
        </first>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
The Whispering Wood is an ancient forest lying on the edge of Farmfields. For generations, the ash and oaks have supplied Sevgard with thick, durable lumber and inspired many artists by their vibrant colors. When the harvest moon arrives, the woodcutters chop trees mercilessly, yet they regrow by the snow's thaw.

Not much is known about the Whispering Wood. Trailblazers constructed a crude path through the forest, yet the environment constantly changes. The path leads north one day and east the next. In fact, the tree leaves are heavily imbued with mana and create a whispering effect which provides magical energy to bypassing wizards. On silent nights, the whispers carry beyond the woodland and reach Farmfields. The strange whispers unsettle the farmers, and they prefer to keep their distance. Perhaps when a cartographer successfully maps the forest, they will make peace with it.

Local legend states that unsavory creatures lurk in its depths. Travelers insist that the whispers grow louder at night and urge them to forsake their way. They see glowing orbs in the distance and mistake them for campfires. The farmers call these creatures will-o'-wisps, and they are curious spirits who can cause powerful delusions. However, there are precautions against these fell creatures. Never stray from the path despite what the whispers say, and always tie a bell to your wrist. The noise will block out the whispers, but it might attract something else.

For instance, goblins reside deep within the forest beneath the roots of a sickly tree. They use the foliage to their advantage and assault anyone traveling the path. When foot traffic is slow, they attack farms and drag livestock away. Nevertheless, local hunters keep the goblins at bay by layering the forest floor with traps. The traps catch goblins and wolves alike, making the woodland a valuable hunting ground.
            ]]>
        </description>
        <level>
            <minimum>6</minimum>
            <maximum>10</maximum>
        </level>
    </exploration>
    <exploration>
        <id>woodland_cemetery</id>
        <target>2</target>
        <name>Woodland cemetery</name>
        <enabled>false</enabled>
        <image>false</image>
        <first>
            <![CDATA[
Pure mystery
            ]]>
        </first>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
Pure mystery
            ]]>
        </description>
        <level>
            <minimum>11</minimum>
            <maximum>15</maximum>
        </level>
    </exploration>
</location>